keen in present of matay and phenomenal
háo hức khi có mặt matay và thật phi thường
completamente spontaneo.
completamente spontaneo.
Completamente
Completamente
Nae.
Nae.
Cannoliso de lamente.
Cannoliso de lamente.
Cannolika.
Cannolika.
Invienemodo mtoterile solamente pokicondi avolte
Invienemodo mtoterile solamente pokicondi avolte
una metora avoltepolique de que.
una metora avoltepolique de que.
Uh,
Ờ,
Jo.
Jo.
To to depend.
Còn tùy.
The Nostrostato
The Nostrostato
the conservadihamo Alivelo Soile.
the conservadihamo Alivelo Soile.
Overeisto dentrodino.
Overeisto dentrodino.
They change the the chakras in Sanskrit.
Họ thay đổi các luân xa trong tiếng Phạn.
Ekpotaojati corso de la nostravitadurante nostravitepaatadiritura.
Ekpotaojati corso de la nostravitadurante nostravitepaatadiritura.
Ewekwado questionergiata kundalini queried the queen a
Ewekwado questionergiata kundalini queried the queen a
loosakro adult respirramesa kwandowenerg as sale.
loosakro adult respirramesa kwandowenerg as sale.
A secondcona
A secondcona
de la di chakra
de la di chakra
porepimenostaolata
porepimenostaolata
nelasheza.
nelasheza.
Quindi la dobeilaka she presented Danechato
Quindi la dobeilaka Bà đã trình bày Danechato
Lakundalini.
Lakundalini.
Obligatory.
Bắt buộc.
Hey
Này
Lalizione iaament and nopotravereluogo.
Lalizione iaament and nopotravereluogo.
Peroquesto uh
Peroquesto ờ
davishamobile rimebile.
davishamobile rimebile.
Abatan Sereta.
Abatan Sereta.
Gracia punto aqueto interventrimajigraanke.
Gracia punto aqueto interventrimajigraanke.
I'll intervene to dele personajalabataji presidentmente.
Tôi sẽ can thiệp vào dele personajalabataji presidentmente.
Choos equally stabilisation.
Chọn sự ổn định như nhau.
I know a possibility,
Tôi biết một khả năng,
a lot of alter.
rất nhiều sự thay đổi.
The adultery person
Người ngoại tình
and phenomenal.
và phi thường.
Kuikoandelache is a port and the alrekandeleeoziva.
Kuikoandelache là một cảng và alrekandeleeoziva.
Quindi nostrata diakuzire
Quindi nostrata diakuzire
Boteroulti noitrata.
Boteroulti noitrata.
Uh
Ờ
Mesa magariti promeodifarekosistane.
Mesa magariti promeodifarekosistane.
Now Ausianopore be Grade.
Bây giờ Ausianopore là Grade.
OKuelodiyoshire a integrachiuto.
OKuelodiyoshire a integrachiuto.
Epomeo adult persona.
Epomeo adult persona.
there.
ở đó.
OK,
Được rồi,
question Gyakundalini.
câu hỏi Gyakundalini.
Quando vienerriviata
Quando vienerriviata
Sale lungo custo canale entrale.
Sale lungo custo canale entrale.
Reativa que entry.
Reativa que lối vào.
Here.
Ở đây.
Connergia primordial leergia only pervate.
Connergia primordial leergia chỉ pervate.
Quelake in Sanskritta Brahmashakti.
Quelake in Sanskritta Brahmashakti.
No kwando questo phenomena vienne kwando quesa vienne.
No kwando questo phenomena vienne kwando quesa vienne.
See the finish yoga yoga punto taperunyone.
Xem kết thúc yoga yoga punto taperunyone.
A sahaja yoga significa uno spontaneaekwa kosake.
A sahaja yoga significa uno spontaneaekwa kosake.
Uh,
Ờ,
in a senskunos forces,
trong một senskunos lực lượng,
OK,
Được rồi,
nato Konnoi.
nato Konnoi.
Uh da Claudio Capuano,
Uh da Claudio Capuano,
a special editor de iano dashiri matai you know
một biên tập viên đặc biệt de iano dashiri matai bạn biết đó
ponoa Westaque mitro di fronte uh la grandadre.
ponoa Westaque mitro di fronte uh la grandadre.
Itsiarla request that doing that uh bison
Itsiarla yêu cầu làm điều đó ờ bison
potenti ohioqui or Alessandra quereuttorosissima mano e ride
potenti ohioqui or Alessandra quereuttorosissima mano e ride
kiose la kundalini.
kiose la kundalini.
persona.
persona.
Is.
Vâng.
umpire steer stand on senso the tranquilia and sensodididi fredo.
umpire steer stand on senso the tranquilia and sensodididi fredo.
Oh.
Ồ.
She would like to touch your hand,
Bà ấy muốn chạm vào tay bạn,
she.
bà ấy.
When I'm touching you,
Khi Ta chạm vào con,
you'll feel the energy flowing into you.
con sẽ cảm nhận được năng lượng chảy vào trong con.
lag flu.
lag flu.
Also you will not
Ngoài ra con sẽ không
have any thoughts in your mind.
có bất kỳ suy nghĩ nào trong tâm trí.
You can watch me without thinking.
Con có thể nhìn Ta mà không suy nghĩ.
You can do that now in sensa moment
Con có thể làm điều đó ngay bây giờ trong sensa moment
passion to the tranquilita is sensari the vertiquesto.
passion to the tranquilita is sensari the vertiquesto.
Because the spirit is the source of joy and what you
Bởi vì spirit là nguồn vui sướng và những gì con
are feeling is the all pervading power of God's love,
đang cảm nhận là Năng lượng Tình yêu Toàn năng của Thượng đế,
which is very subtle.
nó rất vi tế.
Er.
Ờ.
A
A
rise to the las
đi lên đến las
uh.
ờ.
And beautiful person.
Và một người tuyệt đẹp.
Sana unodo at thee.
Sana unodo at thee.
But I segu segula grande madre
But I segu segula grande madre
echo eosa tiao
echo eosa tiao
madatomiadato
madatomiadato
choke noan aginbile put penareulrenarivata yoga and bare percupress etc.
choke noan aginbile put penareulrenarivata yoga and bare percupress etc.
Erique experiment.
Erique experiment.
alto sarani.
alto sarani.
And uh.
Và ờ.
La manifestahamoya um queso fresco with the questo especially the
La manifestahamoya um queso fresco with the questo especially the
the joy to be sent to echo.
niềm vui sướng được gửi đến để vang vọng.
and then stress and Tria yoga sia mima.
and then stress and Tria yoga sia mima.
sun.
mặt trời.
Noun sane um conjun so it's a system and
Noun sane um conjun vì vậy nó là một hệ thống và
booakelanatura uh catalitaguto quidien years since a delay.
booakelanatura uh catalitaguto quidien years since a delay.
Per
Per
bow tian ele aquista
bow tian ele aquista
ibis.
ibis.
I had to put the masa.
Ta đã phải đặt masa.
a divas.
a divas.
Sea justuwere de la sera republica sul tempo.
Sea justuwere de la sera republica sul tempo.
Uh,
Ờ,
queen akwaliwe he would like to know from you if
queen akwaliwe anh ấy muốn biết từ Mẹ rằng liệu
this interview if you are satisfied with his interview.
buổi phỏng vấn này, liệu Mẹ có hài lòng với buổi phỏng vấn của anh ấy không.
Very much,
Rất hài lòng,
very much
rất hài lòng
mosa que bobo questa transmission puttino which is in tiamo boni.
mosa que bobo questa transmission puttino which is in tiamo boni.
E.
E.